I long for tires like these.
Hey!
Isn't this street car awesome?
I'm in love
Step into it
Oh my!
Thank you for your hard work
Hello everyone
I'm Suzuka Otomita from Hyugaizuka46.
Today's project is
Anyway, I'm going to buy Ruma.
Wow!
I've been thinking about buying a car since I started working in motorsports last year, and I'm already 22 years old.
I thought it might be time to buy my first car, so I came to WOW Town Makuhari today.
I want to tell you first that I will definitely buy a car.
I want to say this first, but I will definitely buy a car.
Thank you for looking for a car today, and I'll show you around.
What kind of car are you looking for?
What's the budget for a woman in her 20s?
I think most of them are looking for a car from before to 3,000,000 yen.
I'm sure there are a lot of women who are looking for a car in that price range.
The actuality that there are a lot of women who are looking for a woman's handbag is a good thing.
The most important thing to remember is that you can't go wrong with a good quality product.
I'm sure you'll be able to find a lot of them.
I'll give you a quick tour.
I'm done with the counseling.
If there's anything I don't understand, I'll ask.
I'd like to go in.
I'm sure it's cute, so I'll go in.
It's a really big place.
It's a big place, about the size of Yen's house.
Where shall we start?
But I said I was interested in SUVs.
I think I'll start with the SUV.
Wow!
Wait!
That's not good.
Matsuda Red.
It's called Soul Red.
Wow, beautiful car, too!
That's the color I'd most honestly like to drive.
Wow!
Wait a minute.
Oh, my God.
No, but we have to see more.
It's so beautiful.
Wow.
Wow! It's really Japanese!
That's exactly what I'm talking about.
Wow, I like this grayish one too.
But...
Um...
CX-30?
and the CX-3 red.
Are they the same?
No, it's a different color.
No, they're not, are they?
You know exactly what I mean.
It's a completely different color.
I see.
I like the CX-30 better.
Here it comes! The big one!
Big time?
I love the CX-5 so much.
It's my favorite car to look at.
But I think it's a little big for me when I drive it.
You were looking at the 30 and 3 earlier.
So it's bigger than those?
Yes, they are.
But it's cool.
What's that again? Are these the same? The color.
This one? I think it's the same color as before.
But it's so shiny even in the rain.
Look at this.
It's a nice car, even in the rain.
It's a nice car.
Nice.
Cute.
Here.
I knew the front grille of the car would give it character.
Cute.
Liz, it's cute!
I'll go for a ride.
Okay, excuse me.
It's spacious.
It's so comfortable!
I feel like it fits Japanese people very well.
I think I like it.
I think it fits me very well.
Rise
That's good.
Thank you very much.
I like it.
I like Lasse.
Harrier.
Wait.
Wait!
Wait, this is so cool!Wait, this is so cool.
Here it is again.
This new one over here.
New one?
Oh no!
I want to take a picture with it.
This is the new Haria.
The new Harrier.
Oh, wait.
May I take a look inside?
Please, please, may I try it?
Excuse me.
Whoa, wait.
Wow.
I can sleep in this.
This is so cool!
Oh, I mean, look at the feet.
Is that a Harian symbol?
Yes, it is.
This is great.
It's a little big, isn't it?
It's one step bigger than the bezel.
But I think it's love at first sight.
Isn't this brown Lexus amazing?
It's so austere!
Wow, I like this color.
Oh, this is nice!
NX
Stylish interior!
It's so cool!
Oh, wait a minute.
I want to go over there.
Wow, cool.
Wait a minute.
I want to show you guys.
Isn't this so cool?
Oh, man.
I wonder if people who go surfing ride along the ocean on this thing?
That's for sure.
I kinda like it.
I've never surfed or camped before.
But if I buy a car like this, I might start going!
It's a little big, but I think it's a good idea.
People who buy a big car for the first time...
Oh, wait.
This is also a Love Four.
It's right by the entrance.
Isn't it cute?
Isn't this Love Four cute?
I look so suspicious!
I'm so excited.
There were a lot of nice cars.
But, you know, it's important to be able to see cars from different manufacturers like this.
It's important to be able to see cars from different manufacturers.
I'm so happy!
I drive a Porte.
I want to do it next time.
Thank you.
Sue ・・・・・・・ Spyro is aware of one penitent word.
Starman Disco Spyro, comes
The big one ・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・ ・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・ ・・・・・・・・・・ ・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・ ・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・ ・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・ ・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・ ・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・ ・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・ ・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・ ・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・・ ...
by H.
Oh no.
I'm in love.
I'm in love... completely in love... with this.
Can I get on it now?
It's all right.
Let's go take a look in the back.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
You opened the door for me, and now I'm going to go look in the back.
I'm going to step into my favorite Gemini Sierra.
I'm stepping into it.
Wow.
Oh, you're doing better than I thought you would.
I can see all around me.
I feel like I'm in the middle of nowhere.
I thought the distance, the sense of distance
I thought it might be too small.
Let me show you inside.
Let me show you.
It's like this.
Isn't it cute?
It's totally spacious.
In terms of size...
Compared to other cars.
Compared to other cars?
Eventually, but...
I bought it about the same size as the other cars.
width and so on.
I see. Well, then...
I could totally ride it.
It's cute, isn't it?
No, I know what you mean.
There's yellow, but...
I don't think we have a red one.
But...
Oh, you have yellow?
I think we have yellow.
We have yellow in Jimmy's.In Jimmy's, there's yellow.
But if it were a Jimmy...
I'd definitely go for khaki or this beige.
or this beige.
We have khaki.
Do you have khaki?
Yes, we do.
That's what we're going with.
No, no, no, not yet.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
More than beige.
It's the highest grade.
Plain.
Wow, wait a minute. That's high-end.
These are Michelin tires.
These are Dunlop tires.
If you look at those tires on a woman...
Super GT.
Different tires.
It's all wrong, isn't it?
I adore these tires.
I wouldn't mind if they were all Makro.
I can do very good things.
I can do something really good
I can do something really good!
You're going to paint them?
I'll paint it.
It's the top of the ranks.
Top, top, top.
Because the interior is already
Even before painting...
It's kind of Japanese style, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Japanese-style interior.
Excuse me.
I like it.
Oh, wait, upstairs.
This is the plain one.
Uh...
It's standard equipment.
Oh, shit.
Top is open.
Oh, wow, that's great!
Oh, wow.
All of it.
And they can be tightened.
So even if it's bright...
Even if it's bright.
Wow!
I'd love to ride in this on a sunny day.
It's pretty nice.
I guess the higher the grade, the better.
The interior...
I see.
I can't help it.
I guess you can't resist.
Wow, it's nice!
It's so nice.
Excuse me.
Let's close it up.
Aww.
Super nice.
It's a little difficult.
You had a little extra trouble?
Yes, it was a little difficult.
But it's a space that makes you feel at home.
Oh, I like it. I like it.
I like it.
I've seen a lot.
I think I'll sleep well today By the way, some of the cars here can be bought with the budget I mentioned at the beginning
I don't have a budget for Jimmy and Jimmy Scherer Rise.
I'm afraid this play is a little out of my league.
This is this bezel? That's not in the budget either.
I don't know what I'm going to do.
No, but in my opinion - no, it's all good - what should I do, really?
I want it all... I want it all...
But do you have a grade? You can get yourself a Sierra or something.
Sierra has grades, of course. We have automatic and manual.
Oh, I see.
Is there anything with this interior that, you know, looks good?
Uh, no.
Well, then, today. Buy it today or not.
Tomita, the car.
I'll buy it!
I can't afford 1,000 yen!
I have a lot more candidates today!
I still have a few more cars I want to see.
I have some sports cars that I want to look at.
There are many cars that I want to buy.
I think I'm one step closer to buying one.
Which one would you like to see yourself in?
Yes, I would.
Okay, let's just...
Let's end this in front of the Jimmy.
Next time, I'd like to go and look at some different cars.
But you guys, um, don't worry.
I'll definitely buy it.
Please subscribe to our channel and click the Good button!
That's all for now, I'm Sugi Tomita from Hyugaizaka 46.
See you again!See you soon.
Bye bye!
Please subscribe to our channel!